♪The night wind shakes off
the withered leaves♪
♪I open the window and gaze at the moon♪
♪Haze spreads across the river,
lanterns drifting♪
♪I hear the memories rustling♪
♪Garden flowers shed petals one by one♪
♪Candlelight flickers,
swaying with melancholy♪
♪I sigh by the lamp over the long night♪
♪Past memories unfold scene by scene♪
♪It's all your face♪
♪Boldly trampling over my heart♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for love miswritten♪
♪And another for youth passed♪
♪With endless sorrow,
I once traced your silhouette♪
♪Two measures of ink I take,
one for joy and sorrow♪
♪And another for parting and reunion♪
♪I write until splendor fades,
and I am no more♪
=Prelude of the White Snake=
=Episode 7=
Congratulations!
You look so handsome today.
Don't stare at me.
It's improper.
Congratulations!
Come in.
May you grow old together!
Thank you, thank you.
- Thank you.
- May you have children soon!
Thank you.
Can you stop looking like
you're about to crash the wedding?
Isn't your sister trying to
bond with Xu Xian?
Think of today as a rehearsal.
You are so handsome.
Would you like to be my partner?
So thin-skinned?
Too hard.
First bow to Heaven and Earth!
Second bow...
To Heaven and Earth this way!
They should have left it
to professionals.
This monk is so unprofessional.
Third bow...
Bow to each other!
To the bridal chamber!
- Great!
- Wonderful!
My dear...
As of today, we are married.
My lady...
Yes.
What did you just call me?
My... my...
Do I look that old to you?
No.
Come, time for our nuptial wine.
Right.
Since we have drunk the nuptial wine,
we are a real married couple now.
We're just acting.
Don't take it seriously.
If we don't make it look real,
how can we fool the Rakshasa Bird?
My dear...
After drinking the nuptial wine,
next...
My dear...
Does it have to be so fast?
Next, we should wait for our prey.
Or were you hoping to make it real?
Of course not.
Commit to the bit.
I'm not going to eat you alive.
You really are a demon.
You knew all along?
I only pretended to be close to you
these past few days
to verify your identity.
Did you really think I fell for you?
Snake demon, you killed my parents!
I will kill you!
I didn't! I was undergoing
my tribulation that day.
Pay for my parents' lives!
Xu Xian!
It really was you!
I don't remember anything from that day.
There must be a misunderstanding!
Only if I regain my memories...
How could this pain compare to
what my parents suffered?
How could it compare to
the agonizing pain
I've endured every day and night
for over ten years?
This wedding night
is my final gift to you.
Die in your dreams!
Just a vengeful spirit
Dare act wild before me?
How is this possible?
How could anyone escape my nightmare?
You petty Rakshasa bird, hiding in
dreams after death to harm people.
Stay out of this!
Everyone here is fast asleep?
Yes.
Release them.
With your meager power,
if you don't want your soul shattered,
I suggest you do as I told you.
Wait.
(If I just break
the nightmare like this,)
(Xu Xian will get suspicious
when he wakes up.)
Put on an act with me later.
What kind of world is this?
All lovers must die!
Even in death, I'm being enslaved.
Fahai!
Impure earth, pure heaven.
Clear the mind, break the illusion!
Oh no, we were trapped
in the spirit's illusion.
She has already appeared.
Miss Bai! Miss Bai!
Wake up.
She's here?
Die!
All lovers must die!
Miss Bai, stay here.
You should fight him a bit longer,
and then let yourself be captured.
Make it look convincing.
Just act like how you tried to
hurt people just now.
Just don't let them see
that you fear me, got it?
But don't actually hurt them.
Otherwise...
Sweetie, a word of advice.
Don't ever believe in love.
A monk from Jinshan Temple?
Traitor, pay with your life!
I lost.
Do whatever you want with me.
Ma'am, take a good look at me.
Why are you attacking me?
Do I even know you?
Everyone from Jinshan Temple
deserves to die!
We're not here for revenge.
We have some questions for you.
About what?
The groom who deceived you
and slaughtered
your entire clan,
who was he?
The groom...
(We met and fell in love
with each other.)
(He disregarded the boundary
between mortal and demon)
(and swore to spend his life with me.)
(Yet he gouged out my core
with his own hands)
(and slaughtered my entire clan.)
(All his elaborate schemes)
(were just to steal the cores
of our Rakshasa clan.)
(The reason he played
such a grand scheme)
(and pretended to love me)
(was that our Rakshasa cores,)
(when filled with
utmost despair and sorrow,)
(are most nourishing to cultivators.)
- Changming?
♪I also gave my youth to someone♪
♪I must admit, you made the journey♪
♪When loving you
became instinct, what's left♪
♪Seals a fate too brutal to amend♪
♪Clumsy and new, we gave our first kiss♪
♪Never thought passionate eyes
would turn cold♪
♪I thought of pulling away,
but I'd barely begun♪
♪Having loved you so deep,
how could I love another♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I'm stubborn,
I never stopped you from loving others♪
♪I shouldn't have been so foolish
to think there was still hope♪
♪But you won't even admit what we had♪
♪Even if we're strangers again,
why deny we loved♪
♪Though I have questions,
I never questioned you♪
♪I'll lock you away and set myself free♪
♪After all, I'm the one you deny♪
♪Having ever loved♪